spotfav.com 2015-06-11

# Spotfav, check before you go

##  OUR PROMISE 

Spotfav Reporting Technologies S.L. (Spotfav) respects your privacy and promises to earn and keep your trust. At Spotfav, we understand the importance of privacy, and we want you to be as comfortable as possible visiting our site and using its services. All information about you is kept confidential and will not be used in ways that you have not consented, and we will not sell or disclose any information that identifies you to a third party without your explicit approval. We may disclose personally identifiable information in response to legal process, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency's request, or where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our terms of use, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our sites and applicable laws or as otherwise required or permitted by law or consistent with legal requirements. 

Questions regarding this policy and our practice should be directed to Spotfav, by e-mail to [webmaster@spotfav.com](mailto:webmaster@spotfav.com)

###  Privacy Policy 

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the [Terms and Conditions](http://www.spotfav.com/terms "Terms and Conditions") of use. It tells you what information we collect, how we protect it and what choices you have about how that information is used. Most information collected is to enable us to best meet your needs as an action sports participant in a highly customized and responsive manner. 

###  Under Age 13 

Spotfav does not allow children under the age of thirteen (13) to register because Spotfav must comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, which prohibits the online collection of personal information from people under 13. 

###  Public Forum Discussions and Comments 

Please note that any information that you reveal in a public forum (such as comments) will be seen by third parties not related to Spotfav and is therefore not subject to this privacy policy. 

##  SECTION 1 - PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT 

We collect information in four distinct areas: 

  1. Alerts / Newsletter subscriptions: name, e-mail address 
  2. Membership enrollment and Profile creation: name, address, phone number, password. All Personal information is protected by your password. 
  3. Location: We may collect and store information about your location if you enable your computer or mobile device to send us location information. You may be able to change the settings on your computer or mobile device to prevent it from providing us with such information. Location data is not shared with 3rd. party sites, advertisers or sponsors. 

Spotfav does not store any credit card information. 

##  SECTION 2 - USE AND DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION 

Personal information will not be released to third parties without your explicit permission. 

##  SECTION 3 - SECURITY 

We use encryption and authentication tools to protect the security of Personal information that you share with us. However, no data transmission over the Internet (or, with respect to our mobile services, over cellular phone networks) can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect Personal information, we cannot and do not guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to or from the Site, and you do so at your own risk. 

We restrict access to Personal information to Spotfav employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations. 

##  SECTION 4 - COLLECTION OF INFORMATION BY THIRD-PARTY SITES, AD SERVERS, SPONSORS 

Some of our sites contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Visitors should consult the other sites' privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties. 

Spotfav sites covered by this privacy statement sometimes may offer content (e.g., contests, sweepstakes, or promotions) that is sponsored by or co-branded with identified third parties. By virtue of these relationships, the third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the site activity. We have no control over these third parties' use of this information. The site will notify you at the time of requesting personally identifiable information if these third parties will obtain such information. 

##  SECTION 5 - UPDATING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION AND CONTACTING SPOTFAV 

You can always contact us in order to delete your Personal information from our systems by e-mailing us at webmaster@spotfav.com. You can always update the Personal information that you have provided to us and change your Privacy choices by updating your section on the web site. 

##  CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY 

Spotfav may change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting revisions to our site. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most such changes will be minor. In the event that any changes are made to use of your Personal information, you will be informed via e-mail, and will afford you the opportunity to opt-out of any further use. Your use of the site constitutes acceptance of the provisions of this Privacy Policy and your continued usage after such changes are posted constitutes acceptance of each revised Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy or any revised policy, please exit the site immediately.
